import { QuizSet } from '../../../_types';

export const basicVocabulary1: QuizSet = {
  id: 1,
  name: "Podstawowe słownictwo 1",
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Co oznacza słowo 'wcale'?",
      options: [
        "not at all",
        "again",
        "immediately",
        "easy"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Co oznacza 'znajdować/znaleźć'?",
      options: [
        "to rent",
        "to find/to locate",
        "to look",
        "to translate"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Co oznacza 'patrzeć'?",
      options: [
        "to move",
        "to receive",
        "to look",
        "to translate"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Co oznacza 'ogłoszenie'?",
      options: [
        "rent",
        "advertisement",
        "easy",
        "again"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Co oznacza 'znowu'?",
      options: [
        "immediately",
        "not at all",
        "again",
        "at all"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Co oznacza 'czynsz'?",
      options: [
        "rent",
        "advertisement",
        "to move",
        "to receive"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Co oznacza 'w ogóle'?",
      options: [
        "immediately",
        "at all",
        "easy",
        "should"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Co oznacza 'przeprowadzić się'?",
      options: [
        "to receive",
        "to rent",
        "to move",
        "to translate"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Co oznacza 'odebrać'?",
      options: [
        "to receive",
        "to look",
        "to move",
        "to find"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Co oznacza 'wynająć'?",
      options: [
        "to move",
        "to rent",
        "to translate",
        "to receive"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Co oznacza 'przetłumaczyć'?",
      options: [
        "to move",
        "to look",
        "to translate",
        "to find"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "Co oznacza 'natychmiast'?",
      options: [
        "immediately",
        "again",
        "at all",
        "easy"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "Co oznacza 'powinien'?",
      options: [
        "easy",
        "should",
        "again",
        "immediately"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: "Co oznacza 'łatwy'?",
      options: [
        "should",
        "immediately",
        "easy",
        "at all"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2
    }
  ]
};
